mathopolis.com 2012-03-06

# Privacy Statement at Mathopolis

_This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Mathopolis.com This privacy statement advises you of what information may be collected via this website and what will happen to it._

_1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site  
2\. The organization collecting the information   
3\. How the information is used   
4\. With whom the information may be shared   
5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information   
6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Mathopolis.com control   
7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. _

**_If you feel that we are not abiding by our privacy policy,contact us _**

**Information Collection and Use**

Mathopolis.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Mathopolis.com collects only enough information from our users to provide basic functionality, at several different points on our website. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user's visit. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Some of our partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Log Files: We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Sharing: We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Mathopolis.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Newsletter**   
We do not operate a newsletter. 

**Membership**

If a user elects to become a member we ask for a "username" (not a real name) and an email address. Mathopolis.com stores this information for the sole purpose of handling user-specific information, responding to a specific request, protecting individual safety, or to protect the security or integrity of the website. This information is not made public or disclosed to third parties. 

**Security**

As Mathopolis.com is a free service and sells no products directly there is no secure server connection. At no time will Mathopolis.com directly request address or payment details. However, some partner sites do sell direct. Where possible it has been checked that these sites are using a secure server. Please check as Mathopolis.com cannot be responsible for insecure transactions from other web sites. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
